https://perverx.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyDisclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or SafetyYour name, physical address, phone number and password are considered confidential.However, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system.Information We Collect From YouDuring sign up we require that you provide us with certain information which may include Account Data (i.e., your name, physical address, email address, phone number, username, and password), along with “Demographic Information”.Demographic Information may include IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding search history, browsing history, registration and user history.How is this Information Used?We may use “cookies” and Demographic Information to better your experience on the Site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Sites according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Demographic Information.Aggregate, non-individual membership Demographic Information may be shared with third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products or services we believe you may be interested in.We may also share the aggregate Demographic Information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the Sites.You Are Responsible For Information You Provide to Third PartiesWe process credit card transactions via industry standard encryption through third party processors, which processors only use your information for that purpose.Financial Data is considered private information and will not be shared by us with third parties except with your authorization and as necessary to carry out orders placed by you with the understanding by you that such transaction(s) may be subject to the rules and policies of such third party.Financial or other Data provided by you to any companies or websites advertising on the Sites or in response to emails sent to you by the Sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy.Any information provided by you to a third party, and any transaction with such a third party, is subject to that third party’s terms and conditions and privacy policy.Emails From Us and Use of Your Email AddressYour email address will be used by us to contact you when we have special offers or other information to provide you.Such information may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to your account and other information related to your subscription to this Site.If at any time you no longer wish to receive emails from us you follow th link at the end of the meil.Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our marketing partners without your consent.Please immediately report any emails you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purport to promote this site.AdvertisementsWe may utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties.Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or “action tags” to measure advertising effectiveness on an “anonymous basis”.Some emails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to this site.Should you elect to visit any such advertiser’s website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers’ websites.If you choose to make any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from such companies, we may provide your information, including Financial Data, to the advertiser as necessary to your request. Finally, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the privacy policies or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our service, whether through our website or emails, this is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all of this site on such advertisers’ website(s).Changes to the Privacy PolicyWe may change this privacy policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes.Instead it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. No change in the privacy policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless the privacy policy has clear language indicating otherwise.Changes in the Ownership of the Sitesperverx.com is a growing online service.As such, we may have the occasion to buy or sell assets, including but not limited to merger, dissolution, and transfer of ownership.Depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us (including Account Information) with third parties, as necessary to initiate, investigate or complete any such transaction(s).
Facebook
Twitter
Google Plus ADULT WARNINGWARNING! ADULTS ONLY!If you are under 18 years of age, or if it is illegal to view adult material in your community, please leave now. We can't be held responsible for your actions. We are not acting in any way to send you this information; you are choosing to receive it! Continuing further means that you understand and accept responsibility for your own actions, thus releasing the creators of this Web page and our service provider from all liability. By Entering This Site You Agree That:
You are an adult in your community where you live and you have reached the age of at least 18 years old (21 in some communities);
You will not expose minors to the sexually explicit content you are about to view;
You believe that sexually explicit material is not offensive or obscene;
The community in which you live does not believe sexually explicit material to be obscene or illegal and agrees to view such material;
You agree to use the material available on this website for personal use and will not sell, distribute, give or make available the content for any other person.
You agree to take the appropriate steps to ensure that no minor is able to view the content available on this website;
You read and understood this agreement and declare the binding.
If minors have access to your computer, you agree to use one of the following products to restrict access to sexually explicit material: Cybersitter | Net Nanny | Cyberpatrol | ASACP | SupportAll models were 18 years or older at the date of production which has been documented diligently.
You may not use this site if you're not at least 18 years of age or do not meet the age requirement to watch explicit pornography
set forth by your respective domestic law. World wide Copyright
all rights reserved 18 U.S.C. 2257 Record Keeping Requirements Compliance Statement
Enter
ExitAccess DeniedYou have been denied access to this content. If you feel this is in error, please contact a site administrator.
ExitStay Connected ! Enter your Email Address and you will receive Free UpdatesYou'll also receive a Free Exclusive PerverX HQ Photo-Set in your next NewsletterAdd our address no-reply@trafficmediagroup.org to you contact list, if you like, to be sure we will not be flagged as spamFirst name or nicknameEmail By continuing, you accept the privacy policy
